

ASocial Media Specialist with two years of experience specializing in digital marketing, brand messaging, copywriting, and content marketing. Adept at defining creative strategies to maximize campaign performance and customer engagement. HubSpot certified in content, email, and inbound marketing.

meli ssa a nd erson^Jexample.Mm (123) 456-7890 <u>Linkedln | Portfoli</u>o

Professional Experience

Social Media Coordinator

TriFecta Technologies, Miami, FL | February 2022 - Present

- Leverage Google Analytics and Facebook Insights to evaluate campaign performance, develop reports on social media effectiveness, and identify opportunities to refine marketing approach
- Verily compliance of all brand content with company SEO and SMO strategies and approve the release of all company-owned social media
- I n crea se bl og t ra ffi c by 300% i n eight mo nth s by sha ri n g posts accom pa n ied by creative copy on all company social media platforms, including Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn

Social Media Assistant

Self-Employed, Miami, FL | June 2021 - February 2022

- Grew the company's Instagram audience by 200% within one year by analyzing market d ata a n d i m provi ng messagi ng to better a lign co nten t wi th ta rget audiences
- Created engaging text, graphics, and video content for multiple social media channels
- Increased favorable brand-related material on social media by collaborating with influencers

Education

Miami, FL 12345

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) Marketing Miami Dade College, Miami, FL September 2017 - June 2021

Key Skills

- Social Media Strategy
- ♦ Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Crisis Communication
- Public Relations
- Content Marketing

Certifications

- Content Marketing Certification,
 HubSpot Academy, 2022
- Social Media Marketing
 Certification, HubSpot Academy,
 2021